you're too slow let's see some fire run like you mean it we're running out of sunlight
swing those arms more and throw your legs forward yes sir
i want to hear all of you scream
foreign
Oh
You can't move forward without
Stamina if anything I'm making your lives easier. It starts with the basics basics
With that stamina you won't last even a second with Shina Zugawa and don't get me started on Kanroji's training you slacker
It's hell
And it's hell here too
There's only hell in store for us
Come on, keep it together damn it. Oh geez
Hey, that you Kamado long time. No see kid
Yes
It's good to see you again. I'm so glad you've recovered mr. Uzoi. Ah, well, I don't know if you can call this recovered
I
Hear you managed to take on another upper rank you should count yourself lucky to have all your limbs intact
I certainly do. I'm just thankful. I managed to survive right now
Now then are you ready to work off all that rust you've built up?
Yes, I can't wait
Don't you like to get their fire right now?
I missed everything
Hey!
Good to see you!
Tanjiro, you're back!
Well, it's about time.
It's been a while. It's good to see you.
Thank you for all that you did for me.
Hey, what's with all the formality, huh?
We should be the ones who are thanking you.
Training must be going well.
Mm-hmm. You look manly.
You guys need to be eating a lot more!
If you don't eat, the afternoon session will be even harder!
What?
If you don't finish your meal,
I'll just have to add more drills to the session.
We'll eat! We'll eat!
Guess I will, too.
Eda! Please, have as much as you want.
Great! Thanks for the meal!
If you boys don't empty this pot,
Lord Tengen is gonna tack on more drills!
Listen, you're taking care of patrol tonight, right?
Yeah.
Wanna switch with me?
Not a chance!
Because if you go on night patrol,
you get to be excused from training the next morning.
Give it to me!
We sure haven't been seeing any demons lately, have we?
That fact alone is enough to make my skin crawl.
Get this. I hear it's because the demons are searching for a girl named Nezuko.
That's just speculation, isn't it?
It's not like anyone actually asked a demon in person.
Well, yeah, that's true.
But wouldn't it be great if they were gone and it was like this forever?
That's probably wishful thinking.
I mean, demon slaying has been going on for a thousand years now.
Hey, where'd you go?
Who knows? One could pop up like this any moment.
Don't be such a jerk!
Sorry. My bad.
Hey, enough is enough, okay?
We have to stay focused.
Okay.
Right!
Time for the next drill!
Split up into pairs!
Here I go!
So fast!
Come on now!
Show me what you're made of, damn it!
So there's no way you can fight an upper rank unless you have stamina like that?
Those upper ranks are insanely strong, right?
You wouldn't believe the stuff they can do.
But what was it like?
Well, let's see.
There'd be a pow and you'd already be hit.
But the fact that you're not dead means you could respond in time to turn around,
only to get slammed by them again!
Then you feel a big crunch!
And if that cuts off the oxygen to your brain...
All right, that's enough.
I think we get it.
Sounds like it's a world far beyond the comprehension of us ordinary folks.
All right!
To wrap things up for today, let me see.
You're hitting that mountain!
Take a lap around its foot and come back!
What?
If you don't get a move on, you're not gonna eat!
Come on, guys, run like you mean it!
If you can't even take this, you're not gonna cut it!
He means well.
Lord Tengen has a way with words.
Sure does.
But he's actually a softie.
Just the other day, he refused to even eat his meal.
Until the last slayer came back.
In the end, he went all the way to the mountain to get him.
You know I heard all of that, right?
The Master put these swordsmen in my care, so I'm not about to let them burn out under my watch.
Of course not!
I'll be heading out then!
Sounds good.
That'll get you warmed up.
Everyone with the potential to become a Hashira is kind deep down inside!
Excuse me, can I have another tray, please?
You got it!
I can't take much more of this, but I've got to win!
Or I won't be able to keep my promise to the Master!
I've got to do all I can to keep pushing forward, so Mr. Giyu will join us!
Can I get another?
You got it!
So if I lose, I have to agree to come back and take part in the training, right?
But does that mean I don't have to if I win?
What?
Well, that's not...
Here you go!
One for you too!
Mr.
Please bring him another one.
Will do!
After this tray, I'm calling it quits.
Meaning, if you eat that extra order of noodles, you'll have defeated me in this battle.
And if I take part in the Hashira training after that, you'll be satisfied then, right?
Yes!
Very much!
All right.
Then finish your noodles.
Right!
Mr. Giyu, I'm sure that you could go on eating.
Even so, I feel like I'm about to burst any second now!
Sorry I'm a bit late.
Well, I only just got here myself.
So then, how goes the training?
Never in a million years could I see them becoming assets in a fight against an upper rank.
Yeah, you could say the same thing about mine.
However, training all the core members is what the Master has asked of us.
Yeah.
So, what is it you wanted at this hour?
It's just...
It's been bugging me all this time.
You mean what happened back at that castle?
You and I drove the demons to the brink together.
But just before we dispatched them, they were able to vanish in the blink of an eye.
That many disappearing so quickly is certainly something worth at least looking into.
Yeah.
I've been pondering that myself since then.
What could be behind that door that shut on us?
That there might actually be a demon hideout that we still don't know about.
A demon hideout, huh?
I've been back to that castle several times since then, only to come up empty every time.
It was right around then that demons suddenly vanished from the cities all at once.
So what they're after is Komodo's kid sister.
I have no doubt in my mind that's the case.
Which leads me to believe something big is about to happen soon.
Huh.
Well, whenever that starts, I'll be happy to bring it all to an end.
Don't you think this might be a bad omen for everyone here in the Demon Slayer Corps?
So long as I'm training the Corps members, it keeps me distracted from it all.
But I look at the situation with a dispassionate eye, and I can't help but be aware of the inevitable battle that's to come.
That this calm we're experiencing might be the harbinger of a storm like no other.
Worrying about it isn't going to get us anywhere, though.
While I have you here, I do have a proposal for you.
Heh.
Well, I happen to have one for you, too.
Let me go ahead and tell you mine first.
Take me on in a match, Higuro!
What a coincidence.
That's exactly what I was going to propose to you.
I'm leaving it here, alright?
Oh, thanks, Tanjiro.
That's perfect.
Here, drink this.
It's high-quality gyokuro tea.
It helps with recovering from fatigue.
Really?
Don't mind if I do.
Delicious.
Listen, Tanjiro.
We've been wanting to thank you for what you did at the Entertainment District.
Thank you so much!
Huh?
We're extremely grateful.
Oh, but...
It wasn't just me, so I don't deserve it.
Right, it was you and your younger sister.
That boar-headed kid and the young man with the yellow hair.
And of course, Lord Tengen.
If even one of you hadn't been there, I don't think we could have seen the sunrise that morning.
For Lord Tengen and all three of us to have made it back alive.
When it seemed impossible at one point.
It almost had to be a miracle.
Well...
Not, Zoro.
But...
The truth is, Lord Tengen still wants to keep fighting.
She's right.
He even calls out in his sleep.
He's been blaming himself...
For leaving the core.
Tanjiro...
Please defeat Muzanki, Butsuji.
Right.
I will.
All right, everybody.
Listen up!
Today, I'm calling off the long-distance mountain run that we usually finish up with.
In its place will be a special drill close to actual combat!
To the mountain!
Battles with demons always happen at night.
Which is precisely why we have to hone our combat skills in the darkness.
Strain to see in the dark.
And what you can't see, you'll just have to sense.
Starting now, I'm an enemy demon.
A demon that's going to devour you.
Let's see you try to survive.
And, Komodo, it's your job to be the one who brings me down.
While protecting the rest of these guys.
Hey! Watch out!
He's nearby!
I can't see a thing!
Mr. Uzui's a former shinobi.
So I can't search for his presence by smell.
Where is he?
Where's Mr. Uzui?
Mr. Uzui!
I-impossible!
We don't stand a chance against the Hashira!
Would you say something like that to a demon?
Mr. Uzui is a former Hashira, so we can't be reckless!
We need to have a strategy!
Stay together!
Try and stay close to me!
Stand back to back!
And don't leave yourselves open!
You're too slow!
Slow!
Not too shabby, Komodo.
This strength with just one hand!
He's incredible!
Don't stop there now!
Come at me again!
Right!
Whoa!
They're incredible!
He's managing to hold his own against a former Hashira!
This is an exchange of blows between two people who fought upper ranks and survived!
Your skills have improved, Komodo.
Good work.
You guys!
Ha!
Now you're starting to fight like demon slayers!
Come on!
There's no reason a retired guy like me should be clobbering you like this.
Geez.
Show a little bravado, huh?
We don't stand a chance against you!
Huh?
You're still a former Hashira!
How can we compare?
Give me a break!
I don't remember training you to freak out when things got tough!
But now I know!
Huh?
The Hashira and Komodo might be enough to defeat the upper ranks and Muzan!
This has given me hope!
Me too!
So we're all going to work hard so that one day we can at least support you when you need it!
I promise!
We'll train hard!
And get stronger!
Look at that.
Hm.
You know what?
Despite their flaws, they're still making progress.
But you've learned all you can here, Komodo.
So get a move on.
Right!
We might have defeated some upper ranks, but Muzan Kibutsuji.
Until he's buried beneath us, this will never end.
Counting on you.
Right.
I will defeat him.
Hm.
Here, Tanjiro.
Take this to your next stop, okay?
Bye, everyone.
I'll see you again soon at the next training ground.
Komodo!
You got this!
I'm sure we'll see you around later on!
It's time I go.
Thank you all so much.
Right.
Take care, you.
Give it your best!
Be careful!
Go get him!
Ah!
We have arrived!
Keep working hard!
Please, I can't take this anymore!
What are you talking about?
If you can't even handle this, you're guaranteed to be devoured.
Hey, it's Tokito!
Hey, you.
If this were a real fight, you'd be dead three times over.
If this were a real fight, I'd have had enough ăn to be dead.
This is serious.
Oh
いい
me
Thank you.
Today I'm going to talk about Mr. Uzui.
I've already retired from being a Hashira,
but if you're set on blabbing about me, then make it flashy!
Right. Here's a Taisho-era secret.
He adores hot springs.
He says he healed his wounds at one after the Entertainment District battle.
What's flashy about that?
You need to at least add along with his three gorgeous, amazing wives.
You really love them equally, don't you?
I love those three more than anything else in the world, Kamado.
More Tengen!
They're incredible, aren't they?
Episode 4 to bring a smile to one's face.